Tufts Parents News UP072
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Parents News
1958 -- 2009
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
University Advancement Division
UP072
0.5 Linear Feet
3 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains a single issue from 1958, followed by quarterly issues beginning in 1984. No issues were published between Winter 2003-Spring 2005. Published by the Parents Program. Formerly published as the Parents Bulletin.
- Tufts Parents News, 1958 -- 2009; 1984 -- 2006; UP072.001; 0.5 Linear Feet; 3 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  Published by the Parents Program. Formally published as the Parent's Bulletin.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Tufts Parents Bulletin, 1958; UP072.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Parents News, 1984; UP072.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    Volume, issue
    I, I
  - Tufts Parents News, 1984; UP072.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    I, II
  - Tufts Parents News, Spring, 1985; UP072.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    I, III
  - Tufts Parents News, Freshmen Edition, Fall, 1985; UP072.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Parents News, Fall, 1985; UP072.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    II, I
  - Tufts Parents News, Winter, 1985; UP072.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    II, II
  - Tufts Parents News, Spring, 1986; UP072.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    II, III
  - Tufts Parents News, Freshmen Edition, Fall, 1986; UP072.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Parents News, Winter, 1986; UP072.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    III, II
  - Tufts Parents News, Spring, 1987; UP072.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    III, III
  - Tufts Parents News, Freshmen Edition, Fall, 1987; UP072.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Parents News, Summer, 1991; UP072.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
    VIII, I
  - Tufts Parents News, Winter, 1992; UP072.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
    VIII, 2
  - Tufts Parents News, Summer, 1992; UP072.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
    IX, 1
  - Tufts Parents News, Winter, 1993; UP072.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
    IX, 2
  - Tufts Parents News, Summer, 1993; UP072.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
    X, 1
  - Tufts Parents News, Spring, 1997; UP072.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Parents News, Fall, 1998; UP072.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Parents News, Spring, 2001; UP072.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Parents News, Fall, 2002; UP072.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Parents News, Spring, 2003; UP072.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Parents News, Fall, 2003; UP072.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Parents News, Summer, 2005; UP072.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
    No issues published between fall 2003 and summer 2005
  - Tufts Parents News, Spring, 2006; UP072.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Parent News, Winter, 2006 -- 2007; UP072.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Parents News, Winter, 2008; UP072.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Parents News, Spring, 2008; UP072.001.002.00001; Parents Program
    No volume or issue information.
  - Tufts Parents News, Fall, 2008; UP072.001.002.00002; Parents Program
  - Tufts Parents News, Spring, 2009; UP072.001.002.00003; Parents Program (Box 2)